

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Angular & AngularJs React & React Native CSS & Sass Python (Django Frameworks) Java (Spring, Hibernate) C# (.NET) Amazon Web Services (AWS) MySQL, NoSQL Agile Scrum Team management Marketing & Sales

LANGUAGES

Finnish: Native English: Excellent Swedish: Working skills

PERSONAL SKILLS

Hard worker Reliable and professional Organized Team player Fast learner Motivated

CONTACT

P: +35840 748 4482 E: valimaa.henri@gmail.com

Puistokatu 17 A 18 40100, Jyväskylä Finland

SOCIAL



www.linkedin.com/in/henri-valimaa



www.github.com/henrivalimaa

HENRI VÄLIMAA

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced Full Stack Web Developer with passion of building intuitive software for different user needs. I specialize in creating responsive, dynamic and intuitive UI software but also I'm capable of building RESTful interfaces with handful of techniques.

WORK EXPERIENCE (RELATED)

KEY ACCOUNT MANAGER

Almerin Oy - YlpTree | Jan 2017 - Present

- Managing of client and partner communication
- · Contacting and negotiating with potential partners globally
- Training of sales and marketing team to accomplish company's goals and milestones

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER (LEAD)

Almerin Oy - YipTree | May 2016 - Present

- Developed business logic components and interfaces (REST, Java, Spring, Hibernate)
- Designed and build client software (AngularJs, Sass, Javascript)
- Designed and partly implemented AWS architecture
- Worked as Scrum Master for few different developing teams

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCES

University of Jyväskylä | Jan 2015 - Present (Estimated graduation - 2018)

REFERENCES

Arttu Pekkarinen - CTO - Tarjova Oy

P: +35850 414 7577

E: arttu.pekkarinen@gmail.com